RAYMOND CHUNG

Archung95.github.io ≥12rc51@queensu.ca in raymondchung95 € prchung95

SUMMARY:

I am a developer from Toronto, ON with a love for programming, sports and people. I specialize on teaching, UI/UX Design and Front End Development with an emphasis on usability and relentless attention to detail and visual execution.



EDUCATION

Queen's University

Computer Science (Honours) Graduating May 2017

Queen's University

Concurrent Education Graduating May 2018



SKILLS

Languages:

Python / HTML / CSS / Java / PHP / JavaScript / Swift 2

Technologies:

Bash / Git / Bootstrap / MaterializeCSS / AngularJS / iQuery / Node.is + Express / MEAN Stack

Design:

Photoshop / Illustrator / Sketch 3 / Affinity Design

Interests:

Education, Basketball, Cooking, Soccer

ACTIVITIES

- IT Director of Queen's Startup Summit (2016-2017)
- Member of Software Developer's Club (2016-Present)
- Peer Tutor of a variety of Computer Science courses (2014-Present)

EXPERIENCE

Workshop & Curriculum Developer, Sudo Labs

June 2016 - Present

- Developed the web development workshop and curriculum
- Organization featured in the Kingston Whig newspaper

Research Assistant, Queen's University

May 2016 - Present

- Researching the execution and analysis of UML models to help maximize the potential of Model-Driven Development
- Debugging a code generator that causes deadlock

iOS & Web Developer, COMPSA Web Services

July 2015 - Present

- Developed and maintained websites for student-run clubs and organization using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript and Bootstrap
- Developed and designed mobile applications specifically for Apple products using Swift 2, and mock-ups using Sketch 3

Teaching Assistant, Queen's University

Jan 2016 - April 2016

- Led CISC P81: Computers: Applications & Implications where over 50% of the students got over an 80% final grade
- Proctored, assisted and graded over 90 tests and weekly lab assignments in a consistent and timely manner

Co-Founder, Foody Co

Sept 2016 - April 2016

- Launched a subscription-based healthy meal service targeted towards students
- Responsible for creating and maintaining the website

</> PORTFOLIO

Application Portal, Web Application

- Created an application portal for Queen's Startup Summit to make the delegation process more efficient and effective when handling over 150 applications
- Built using the MEAN stack (MongoDb, Express, AngularJs and Node.is)

DeckLog App, Android

- App that tracks the user's location and logs down the distance travelled and average sailing speed; made for and use by Kingston's Redwood Power & Sail club
- Responsible for the design and front-end of the app
- Developed using Android studio, with SQLite as backend and Adobe Photoshop for design